{
    "id": "7b47a00d97644d619ba9076a7b3b6de2",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Go",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Gambling goes ........................... my principles.",
            "description": "If something goes against your principles, you cannot agree with that. ",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "in",
                "against"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "849423e9b0d8470ab96417f349746490"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has gone ...................... a lot of hardships.",
            "description": "To go through something is to experience it. ",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "out",
                "for",
                "through"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "0bd9175b9aac4b91873cac02506b12df"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will go ...................... these files if I get time.",
            "description": "To go through something is to examine it carefully. ",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "for",
                "across",
                "through"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "049da8d2c8494485aea33eae6e2b23c6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Whether you give us your support or not we will go ......................",
            "description": "To go ahead is to proceed. ",
            "answers": [
                "along",
                "ahead",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0ec1d11cb7004c5791358a4c55907322"
        },
        {
            "question": "I think I am going ...................... with flu.",
            "description": "To go down with flu is to become ill with it. ",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "down",
                "on",
                "ahead"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "34b98dbfc4574989b28312e508a77515"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have we got enough food to go .....................?",
            "description": "Go round  = have enough to serve everybody around",
            "answers": [
                "round",
                "over",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "17d4e29e1db2483d9d7223d947c6db5b"
        },
        {
            "question": "We have gone a bit too far. Don't you think we should go ................... now?",
            "description": "To go back is to return to a previous position. ",
            "answers": [
                "down",
                "back",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "19049b2e31a84517817dee67f9ae7124"
        },
        {
            "question": "Although I hadn't provoked the dog, he went ....................... me.",
            "description": "To go for somebody is to attack them. ",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6554edcd63914c15bda2ef835d1a67de"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don't forget to go ......................... your notes before exam.",
            "description": "To go over notes is to revise them. ",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "after",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3f82f61420a14b7fb93b794fa1ef53bf"
        },
        {
            "question": "Prices of essential commodities have gone .........................",
            "description": "When prices go up, they increase. ",
            "answers": [
                "through",
                "up",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "25f59f2446c6446887c47bc2425004e6"
        },
        {
            "question": "He went ........................ his family business as soon as he had completed his MBA.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "into",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "19feeba527d5443f9e1eb62e031d66fc"
        },
        {
            "question": "James is going ......................... with a French girl.",
            "description": "To go out with somebody is to have a romantic relationship with them. ",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "after",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6d0634a9e41c4e88b74a6a06969908d5"
        }
    ]
}